{
    "id": "1823838daa884422a8369d75b88fa03d",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think I will be staying here for ……………………… more days.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number few means almost none. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48226a308bd1448e9b8a61f7186e5761"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is junior ……………………….. me.",
            "description": "The words junior, senior, superior and inferior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0afc592bafad43f49ed4a5380f6c2bcc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was ………………………… than I thought.",
            "description": "Easier is the comparative form of easy.",
            "answers": [
                "easier",
                "more easy",
                "more easier"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f0161e9b2fcb4e0c8ec6cf539b6432f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… than me.",
            "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever. ",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "more clever",
                "more cleverer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a4dda1e544b460aa1662ce196842600"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please wait …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25f259f376704c4baddef74797b22a4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take ……………………………. of the two routes.",
            "description": "When the comparison is between two people or things, the comparative form is preferred. ",
            "answers": [
                "the short",
                "the shorter",
                "the shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f07e0bf75054864b2ab182db6049187"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… of the three brothers.",
            "description": "When the comparison is among more than two people or things, the superlative form is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "the smart",
                "the smarter",
                "the smartest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "10a3b6b361b14eb68f6149b597c34dc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… than you.",
            "description": "Much can modify comparatives. More cannot modify comparatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "much young",
                "more younger",
                "much younger"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3abd46eb996748088da9cbbdeccccaba"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t earn as much as ……………………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are preferred after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9927671677f243ddb509efc19f538949"
        },
        {
            "question": "Man is ……………………………… intelligent animal.",
            "description": "Use the with superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most",
                "the more"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a58b01439c34ddbb3feba57112b999c"
        },
        {
            "question": "English is widely …………………………….. in India.",
            "description": "In passive structures use the third form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoken",
                "spoke",
                "speak"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de15efb217374a6d9fb7a66dd9c34e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "I love you more than ………………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are preferred after as and than. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "181a1ac2121946fd929b66c62fee4515"
        }
    ]
}